<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SpeakPedia</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="s">S</string>
    <string name="d">D</string>
    <string name="g">G</string>
    <string name="h">H</string>
    <string name="q">Q</string>
    <string name="w">W</string>
    <string name="e">E</string>
    <string name="r">R</string>
    <string name="t">T</string>
    <string name="y">Y</string>
    <string name="u">U</string>
    <string name="i">I</string>
    <string name="o">O</string>
    <string name="p">P</string>
    <string name="a">A</string>
    <string name="j">J</string>
    <string name="k">K</string>
    <string name="l">L</string>
    <string name="z">Z</string>
    <string name="x">X</string>
    <string name="c">C</string>
    <string name="v">V</string>
    <string name="b">B</string>
    <string name="n">N</string>
    <string name="m">M</string>
    <string name="f">F</string>
    <string name="clear">clear</string>
    <string name="game">Game</string>
    <string name="about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="about_speak">About SpeakPedia:\n \nSpeakPedia is a top language-learning tool that addresses the various demands of pronunciation and spelling in plenty of words with translation of various dialects in the Philippines for local or foreigners to use. With a team of dedicated college level programmers, SpeakPedia aims to revolutionize the way people explore words, meanings, and linguistic nuances.\n \nMission and Vision\n \nThe primary mission of SpeakPedia is to empower individuals with the knowledge and tools to enhance their English skills. By providing a comprehensive and reliable Learning app, the team endeavors to make word learning accessible, efficient, and enjoyable for users of all backgrounds and proficiency levels. The team at SpeakPedia is committed to expanding linguistic horizons. In pursuit of our vision, we aim to integrate a unique feature into our app, allowing users to seamlessly translate English to various dialects spoken in the Philippines. This enhancement will further enrich the language-learning experience, fostering inclusivity and connectivity among diverse communities.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUsActivity</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="come_and_ha">Come and have a try to solve our Word Game challenge</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="let">Let\'s improve and Enhance Your Words</string>
    <string name="SpeakPedia">SPEAKPEDIA</string>
    <string name="hint_its_all_fruits">Hint: Its all fruits!</string>
    <string name="del">DEL</string>
    <string name="speak">speak</string>
    <string name="good_job">good job</string>
    <string name="Translate">Translator</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="language_options">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Japanese</item>
        <item>French</item>
        <!-- Add more language options as needed -->
    </string-array>
    <string name="new_splashscreen_msg">a Friendly guide to your everyday convo and tour</string>
    <string name="choose_a_color">Choose a Color:</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
       <![CDATA[
    Speakpedia Terms and Conditions\n\n
    Last Updated: [January 08 2024]\n\n
    Welcome to Speakpedia! These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of the Speakpedia application.\n\n
    By accessing this application, we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use Speakpedia if you do not agree to all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.\n\n
    The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement, and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: &quot;Client,&quot; &quot;You,&quot; and &quot;Your&quot; refer to you, the person accessing this application and accepting the Company\'s terms and conditions. &quot;The Company,&quot; &quot;Ourselves,&quot; &quot;We,&quot; &quot;Our,&quot; and &quot;Us,&quot; refer to our Company. &quot;Party,&quot; &quot;Parties,&quot; or &quot;Us,&quot; refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves.\n\n
    Cookies\n
    We employ the use of cookies. By accessing Speakpedia, you agreed to use cookies in agreement with the Speakpedia\'s Privacy Policy.\n\n
    Most interactive websites use cookies to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used by our website to enable the functionality of certain areas to make it easier for people visiting our website.\n\n
    License\n
    Unless otherwise stated, Speakpedia and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on Speakpedia. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from Speakpedia for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.\n\n
    You must not:\n
    - Republish material from Speakpedia\n
    - Sell, rent, or sub-license material from Speakpedia\n
    - Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from Speakpedia\n
    - Redistribute content from Speakpedia\n\n
    This Agreement shall begin on the date hereof.\n\n
    Parts of this website offer an opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions and information in certain areas of the website. Speakpedia does not filter, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their presence on the website. Comments do not reflect the views and opinions of Speakpedia, its agents and/or affiliates. Comments reflect the views and opinions of the person who post their views and opinions. To the extent permitted by applicable laws, Speakpedia shall not be liable for the Comments or for any liability, damages or expenses caused and/or suffered as a result of any use of and/or posting of and/or appearance of the Comments on this website.\n\n
    Speakpedia reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which can be considered inappropriate, offensive or causes a breach of these Terms and Conditions.\n\n
    You warrant and represent that:\n
    - You are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;\n
    - The Comments do not invade any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark of any third party;\n
    - The Comments do not contain any defamatory, libelous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material which is an invasion of privacy.
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>